let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Tirana  is the capital of?",
        answer: "Albania",
        options: [ "Albania",  "Philippiness", "Uruguay", "Ireland"]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Andorra la vella is the capital of?",
        answer: "Andorra",
        options: [ "Croatia", "France", "Andorra", "Israel" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Vienna is the capital of?",
        answer: "Austria",
        options: ["Austria","Germany","Belize","Cameroon"]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Minsk is the capital of?",
        answer: "Belarus",
        options: ["Ecuador","Belarus","Bulgaria","Iceland"  ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Brussels is the capital of?",
        answer: "Belgium",
        options: ["Norway", "Dominica","Lithuania", "Belgium"]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Sarajevo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Bosnia-Herzegovina",
        options: ["Latvia", "Monaco", "Bosnia-Herzegovina", "Netherlands"]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Sofia is the capital of?",
        answer: "Bulgaria",
        options: ["Portugal","Serbia","Bulgaria","Finland" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Zagreb is the capital of?",
        answer: "Croatia",
        options: ["Liechtenstein","Croatia", "Greece","Slovakia" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Prague is the capital of?",
        answer: "Czech Republic",
        options: ["Czech Republic","Hungary","Macedonia", "Netherlands"]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Copenhagen is the capital of?",
        answer: "Denmark",
        options: [ "Finland","Denmark", "Malta","Romania"]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Tallinn is the capital of?",
        answer: "Estonia",
        options: ["Estonia", "Iceland", "Iran",  "Norway" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Helsinik is the capital of?",
        answer: "Finland",
        options: ["San Marino","Cuba", "Saint Lucia","Finland" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Paris is the capital of?",
        answer: "France",
        options: ["Holy See", "France", "Ireland","Guatemala"]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Berlin is the capital of?",
        answer: "Germany",
        options: [
            "Russia",
            "Mexico",
            "Germany",
            "Philippines"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "Athens is the capital of?",
        answer: "Greece",
        options: [
            "Ukraine",
            "Greece",
            "Montenegro",
            "Romania"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "Vatican City is the capital of?",
        answer: "Holy See",
        options: [
            "San Marino",
            "Latvia",
            "Italy",
            "Holy See"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "Budapest is the capital of?",
        answer: "Hungary",
        options: [
            "Hungary",
            "Angola",
            "Brazil",
            "Chile"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Reykjav√≠k is the capital of?",
        answer: "Iceland",
        options: [
            "Denmark",
            "Iceland",
            "Bahrain",
            "Ireland"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "Dublin is the capital of?",
        answer: "Ireland",
        options: [
            "Ireland",
            "Macedonia",
            "Kenya",
            "Ghana"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "Rome is the capital of?",
        answer: "Italy",
        options: [
            "Morocco",
            "Italy",
            "Poland",
            "Norway"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "Riga is the capital of?",
        answer: "Latvia",
        options: [
            "Serbia",
            "Latvia",
            "Sweden",
            "Costa Rica"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Vaduz is the capital of?",
        answer: "Liechtenstein",
        options: [
            "Israle",
            "Brunei",
            "Liechtenstein",
            "Ethiopia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "Vilnius is the capital of?",
        answer: "Lithuania",
        options: [
            "Lithuania",
            "Latvia",
            "paraguay",
            "Venezuela"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "Luxembourg  is the capital of?",
        answer: "Luxembourg",
        options: [ "Luxembourg",  "Poland", "Haiti", "Egypt"]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Skopje is the capital of?",
        answer: "Macedonia",
        options: [ "Macedonia", "Suriname", "Argentina", "Dominica" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "Valletta is the capital of?",
        answer: "Malta",
        options: ["Namibia","Mali","Malta","Costa Rica"]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "Chisinau is the capital of?",
        answer: "Moldova",
        options: ["Moldova","Canada","New Zealand","Belize"  ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "Monaco is the capital of?",
        answer: "Monaco",
        options: ["Serbia", "Monaco","Lithuania", "Beligum"]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "Amsterdam and The Hugue is the capital of?",
        answer: "Netherlands",
        options: ["Luxembourg", "Netherlands", "Austria", "Latvia"]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "Oslo is the capital of?",
        answer: "Norway",
        options: ["Ireland","Ghana","Bulgaria","Norway" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question: "Warsaw is the capital of?",
        answer: "Poland",
        options: ["Tanzania","Poland", "Japan","Germany" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question: "Lisbon is the capital of?",
        answer: "Portugal",
        options: ["Czech Republic","Hungary","Portugal", "El Salvador"]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question: "Bucharest is the capital of?",
        answer: "Romania",
        options: [ "Poland","Latvia", "Costa Rica","Romania"]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question: "San Marino is the capital of?",
        answer: "San Marino",
        options: ["Serbia", "Saint Lucia", "Sweden",  "San Marino" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 35,
        question: "Belgrade is the capital of?",
        answer: "Serbia",
        options: ["Serbia", "Maldives", "Denmark","Guatemala"]
    },
    {
        numb: 36,
        question: "Bratislava is the capital of?",
        answer: "Slovakia",
        options: ["Slovakia","Netherlands", "Saint Lucia","Spain" ]
    },
    {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Ljubljana is the capital of?",
        answer: "Slovenia",
        options: [
            "Portugal",
            "Malta",
            "Sweden",
            "Slovenia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Madrid is the capital of?",
        answer: "Spain",
        options: [
            "The Bahamas",
            "Greece",
            "Spain",
            "Togo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 39,
        question: "Stockholm is the capital of?",
        answer: "Sweden",
        options: [
            "Philippines",
            "Latvia",
            "Sweden",
            "Finland"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 40,
        question: "Berne is the capital of?",
        answer: "Switzerland",
        options: [
            "Canada",
            "Switzerland",
            "Hungary",
            "Nepal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 41,
        question: "Kiev is the capital of?",
        answer: "Ukraine",
        options: [
            "Ukraine",
            "India",
            "Norway",
            "Guatemala"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 42,
        question: "London is the capital of?",
        answer: "United Kingdom",
        options: [
            "Syria",
            "Ireland",
            "United Kingdom",
            "Finland"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Moscow is the capital of?",
        answer: "Russia",
        options: [
            "Spain",
            "Cambodia",
            "Turkey",
            "Russia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 44,
        question: "Podgorica is the capital of?",
        answer: "Brazil",
        options: [
            "Brazil",
            "Montenegro",
            "San Marino",
            "Moldova"
        ]
    }
];